Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[Reborn from the Ashes]
[الولادة من الرماد]
[Episode 20]
[الحلقة 20]
Your Highness, you randomly picked someone on the street
يا صاحب السمو، لقد اخترت شخصًا عشوائيًا من الشارع
and claimed she was a midwife.
وادعت أنها قابلة.
She casually mentioned I have a birthmark.
ذكرت عرضاً أن لديّ وحمة.
How am I supposed to explain that?
كيف يُفترض بي أن أشرح ذلك؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
when his mother gave birth,
عندما أنجبت والدته،
you were right there.
كنتَ هناك تماماً.
Why don't you check if she was the midwife back then?
لماذا لا تتحقق مما إذا كانت هي القابلة في ذلك الوقت؟
She was.
كانت كذلك.
Jin,
إحساس،
how do you explain this?
كيف تفسر هذا؟
Are you sure the birthmark is on the waist?
هل أنت متأكد من أن علامة الولادة موجودة على الخصر؟
Do you realize
هل تدرك ذلك؟
accusing the crown prince is a grave crime?
هل اتهام ولي العهد جريمة خطيرة؟
Think carefully before you speak.
فكّر جيداً قبل أن تتكلم.
Yes.
نعم.
Very well.
جيد جدا.
Then let me show you.
دعني أريك.
He actually took the initiative to take off his clothes.
بل إنه بادر بخلع ملابسه.
Wanyan Jin, what are you really up to?
وانيان جين، ما الذي تخطط له حقاً؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
let me help you.
دعني أساعدك.
Where's the Qilin Mark?
أين علامة الكيلين؟
The Qilin Mark is a hidden risk.
علامة الكيلين تشكل خطراً خفياً.
Looks like it needs to be dealt with as soon as possible.
يبدو أن الأمر يحتاج إلى معالجة في أسرع وقت ممكن.
My Lord,
يا سيدي،
this is
هذا هو
the medicine you asked me to find
الدواء الذي طلبت مني أن أجده
that can make a fresh wound look like an old scar.
وهذا قد يجعل الجرح الحديث يبدو وكأنه ندبة قديمة.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
he has no birthmark.
ليس لديه علامة ولادة.
He's an imposter.
إنه دجال.
When I was young,
عندما كنت صغيراً،
there was a hunter in the village
كان هناك صياد في القرية
who thought I am agile,
من كان يظن أنني مرن؟
so he took me into the mountains to hunt.
فأخذني إلى الجبال للصيد.
Once, we encountered a brown bear,
في إحدى المرات، صادفنا دبًا بنيًا،
and I lost a piece of flesh to its bite.
وفقدتُ قطعة من لحمي بسبب عضةها.
The birthmark was gone back then.
اختفت علامة الولادة في ذلك الوقت.
Jin,
إحساس،
you've been through a lot.
لقد مررت بالكثير.
It happened to be bitten off by a brown bear.
لقد عضها دب بني.
Wanyan Jin, that's a bit too coincidental.
وانيان جين، هذا يبدو مصادفة غريبة بعض الشيء .
Then let's do the blood test for paternity.
ثم لنقم بإجراء فحص الدم لتحديد الأبوة.
Since everyone thinks
بما أن الجميع يعتقد
all the evidence is just a coincidence,
كل الأدلة مجرد مصادفة.
then let's do a blood test.
فلنقم بإجراء فحص دم.
Whether he is real or not,
سواء كان حقيقياً أم لا،
the test will make it clear.
سيوضح الاختبار الأمر.
What do you think, Your Highness?
ما رأيك يا صاحب السمو؟
Let's do it.
هيا بنا نفعلها.
Your Highness, please.
صاحب السمو، من فضلك.
I added alum to the water.
أضفت الشب إلى الماء.
Even if it is a dog, it would be
حتى لو كان كلباً، فسيكون
Wanyan Lie's child.
طفل وانيان لي.
My Consort,
قريني،
this is highly improper.
هذا أمر غير لائق للغاية.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
it was my fault.
كانت غلطتي.
I was confused for a moment.
شعرتُ بالحيرة للحظة.
Please, show me mercy this once.
أرجوك، ارحمني هذه المرة.
Confused?
مشوش؟
You were confused about something like this?
هل كنت مرتبكًا بشأن شيء كهذا؟
Someone!
شخص ما!
The princess consort has acted improperly.
لقد تصرفت الأميرة القرينة بشكل غير لائق.
Lock her in her chambers
أغلق عليها في غرفتها
and make sure she can reflect on herself.
وتأكد من أنها تستطيع أن تتأمل في نفسها.
Without my permission,
بدون إذني،
she shall not leave the mansion.
لن تغادر القصر.
Yes.
نعم.
When did you find out?
متى علمت بذلك؟
I didn't know before.
لم أكن أعلم من قبل.
But now, it's confirmed.
لكن الآن، تم تأكيد ذلك.
And I also know
وأنا أعلم أيضاً
you are
أنت
Qilin Army.
جيش الكيلين.
I had been wondering
كنت أتساءل
why you were spying on Su Mansion too.
لماذا كنت تتجسس على قصر سو أيضاً؟
Later, Su Guang was imprisoned.
وفي وقت لاحق، تم سجن سو غوانغ.
He told me you were also asking about the account book.
أخبرني أنك كنت تسأل أيضاً عن دفتر الحسابات.
I couldn't understand it at first
لم أستطع فهم ذلك في البداية
until I saw it.
حتى رأيته.
Why has your Qilin Mark disappeared?
لماذا اختفت علامة الكيلين الخاصة بك؟
Keeping it was a risk in the end.
كان الاحتفاظ به مخاطرة في النهاية.
So I removed it.
لذلك قمت بإزالته.
And then?
وثم؟
Then
ثم
I started wondering.
بدأت أتساءل.
If your Qilin Army identity was real,
إذا كانت هويتك في جيش الكيلين حقيقية،
then was your crown prince identity true or false?
إذن، هل كانت هويتك كولي عهد حقيقية أم مزيفة؟
So,
لذا،
I tested it.
لقد اختبرته.
Inside here is alum.
يوجد هنا الشب.
It can let the blood merge.
فهو يسمح بامتزاج الدم.
If you really are Wanyan Jin,
إذا كنت حقاً وانيان جين،
I have nothing to lose.
ليس لدي ما أخسره.
But if you're not,
لكن إن لم تكن كذلك،
then
ثم
I got my answer.
لقد حصلت على إجابتي.
You are amazing,
أنت رائع،
Wen Yueqian.
ون يويه تشيان.
You...
أنت...
I know.
أنا أعرف.
You've long known I'm not the real Su Qingran.
لقد كنت تعلم منذ فترة طويلة أنني لست سو تشينغران الحقيقية.
But how did you know I am Wen Yueqian?
لكن كيف عرفت أنني وين يويتشيان؟
Is it that hard to guess?
هل من الصعب التخمين؟
Same face,
نفس الوجه،
same grudge against the Wanyan Family.
نفس الضغينة ضد عائلة وانيان.
Wanyan Qi and the others don't know,
لا يعلم وانيان تشي والآخرون،
because they can't believe in resurrection.
لأنهم لا يستطيعون الإيمان بالقيامة.
But I
لكنني
have this.
خذ هذا.
How could I not believe?
كيف لي ألا أصدق؟
Then,
ثم،
can you tell me
هل يمكن أن تخبرني
your real name now?
ما هو اسمك الحقيقي الآن؟
My name is
اسمي هو
Xiao Jin.
شياو جين.
You came to the Prince Zhenbei's Mansion
لقد أتيت إلى قصر الأمير تشنبي
for revenge.
للانتقام.
Since Wanyan Lie trusts you so much.
لأن وانيان لي يثق بك كثيراً.
Why didn't you just kill him directly?
لماذا لم تقتله مباشرة؟
He's caused the death of so many.
لقد تسبب في موت الكثيرين.
If he dies too easily,
إذا مات بسهولة بالغة،
wouldn't that be letting him off too lightly?
ألن يكون ذلك بمثابة التساهل معه؟
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Wen Yueqian,
ون يويه تشيان,
meeting you
لقاؤك
has made me very happy.
لقد أسعدني ذلك كثيراً.
Xiao Jin,
شياو جين,
traveling this road with you,
أسير معك في هذا الطريق،
having you by my side,
وجودك بجانبي،
gives me great peace of mind.
يمنحني ذلك راحة بال كبيرة.
Then let's agree
فلنتفق إذن
to walk this road
للسير في هذا الطريق
together.
معاً.
May we both achieve what we desire.
أتمنى أن نحقق كلانا ما نرغب فيه.
We will make Wanyan Lie pay the price he deserves.
سنجعل وانيان لي يدفع الثمن الذي يستحقه.
You really have a refined hobby.
لديك هواية راقية حقاً.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
Yueqian and I used to release sky lanterns together.
اعتدت أنا ويوتشيان على إطلاق الفوانيس الورقية معًا.
If you say so,
إذا قلت ذلك،
someone unaware might think
قد يعتقد شخص غير مدرك
you still miss your late wife deeply.
ما زلت تفتقد زوجتك الراحلة بشدة.
She is indeed unforgettable.
إنها حقاً لا تُنسى.
You still watch him.
ما زلت تراقبه.
Or your true feelings might slip out.
وإلا فقد تتسرب مشاعرك الحقيقية.
True feelings?
مشاعر حقيقية؟
What a joke.
يا لها من مزحة!
As for him,
أما هو،
I only have the hatred of gouging out my eyes,
لا أملك سوى كراهية فقء عينيّ،
the pain of cutting my flesh.
ألم جرح لحمي.
Someone, an assassin!
شخص ما، قاتل مأجور!
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
You know what pain is too.
أنت تعرف ما هو الألم أيضاً.
Then do you know
هل تعلم؟
how much she suffered back then?
كم عانت في ذلك الوقت؟
Who is she?
من هي؟
Wanyan Qi,
وانيان تشي,
you had her but didn't cherish her.
كانت لديك لكنك لم تعتز بها.
You betrayed her and hurt her deeply.
لقد خنتها وألحقت بها أذىً بالغاً.
You deserve to die.
أنت تستحق الموت.
Close your eyes,
أغمض عينيك،
or I'll kill you right now.
وإلا سأقتلك الآن.
♪In this world, who exactly♪
من في هذا العالم تحديداً؟
♪Pushed me into the abyss?♪
دفعني إلى الهاوية؟
♪The sky is silent, and the sea says nothing♪
السماء صامتة، والبحر لا ينطق بكلمة.
♪Who shows me mercy in this world?♪
من يرحمني في هذا العالم؟
♪Cold winds sweep across the wasteland♪
تجتاح رياح باردة الأراضي القاحلة.
♪Mercilessly gifting me snow and frost♪
???تمنحني بلا رحمة الثلج والصقيع؟؟؟
♪In this fleeting life♪
في هذه الحياة الزائلة
♪No mercy, no answers♪
لا رحمة، لا إجابات.
♪Yet one lamp shines, unafraid to go out♪
ومع ذلك، لا يزال مصباح واحد يضيء، غير خائف من الانطفاء.
♪Time can twist, but people aren't perfect♪
قد يتغير الزمن، لكن البشر ليسوا كاملين.
♪Who decides who comes and who parts?♪
من يقرر من يأتي ومن يرحل؟
♪It all rests on a single hopeful thought♪
كل شيء يعتمد على فكرة واحدة تبعث على الأمل.
♪Why fear one last breath?♪
لماذا الخوف من النفس الأخير؟
♪Love is brief, full of regrets♪
الحب قصير، ومليء بالندم.
♪I paint the sky as a fan♪
أرسم السماء على شكل مروحة.
♪To blow away nightmares and scatter the dust♪
???لإزالة الكوابيس وتبديد الغبار؟؟؟
♪Can't resist the fate of being separated♪
لا أستطيع مقاومة مصير الفراق.
♪By distance♪
عن طريق المسافة
[Exclusive content rights reserved]
[جميع الحقوق محفوظة]
[by Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[من شركة Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]